Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
- Box: 38, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Item 61: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1969; Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.26: August 20, 1969
  - Item 62: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1969; Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.27: October 22, 1969
  - Item 63: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1969; Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.28: November 26, 1969
  - Item 64: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1969; Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.29: December 17, 1969
  - Item 65: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1970; Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.30: January 28, 1970
  - Item 66: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1970; Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.31: February 25, 1970
  - Item 67: Industrial News, 1971; Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.22, June 4, 1971
- Box: 38, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: No. 9, April 13, 1967
  - Item 2: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: No. 125, December 1967
  - Item 3: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.22, January 11, 1968
  - Item 4: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.10, April 28, 1967
  - Item 5: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.10, July 5, 1968
  - Item 6: Industrial News, Correction to Industrial News No. 17, October 22, 1969, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.11, July 25, 1968
  - Item 8: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.11, May 10, 1967
  - Item 10: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.12, August 23, 1968
  - Item 11: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.12, May 25, 1967
  - Item 12: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.13, August 29, 1968
  - Item 13: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.13, June 30, 1967
  - Item 14: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.14, July 26, 1967
  - Item 15: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.14, October 2, 1968
  - Item 16: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.15, August 2, 1967
  - Item 17: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.15, October 16, 1968
  - Item 18: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.16, August 31, 1967
  - Item 19: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.16, October 25, 1968
  - Item 20: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.17, September 14, 1967
  - Item 21: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.18, October 14, 1967
  - Item 22: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.19, October 27, 1967
  - Item 23: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.2, January 19, 1968
  - Item 24: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.20, November 24, 1967
  - Item 25: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.21, December 6, 1967
  - Item 26: Industrial News, 1971; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.25, September 24, 1971
  - Item 27: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.3, January 25, 1968
  - Item 28: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.4, February 15, 1968
  - Item 29: Industrial News, 1969; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.5, March 24, 1969
  - Item 30: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.6, March 20, 1968
  - Item 31: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.7, March 28, 1968
  - Item 32: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.8, April 26, 1968
  - Item 33: Industrial News, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.8, April 6, 1967
  - Item 34: Industrial News, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.9, May 23, 1968
  - Item 35: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.1, May 1967
  - Item 36: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.10: March 1968
  - Item 37: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.11: April 17, 1968
  - Item 38: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.12: May 22, 1968
  - Item 39: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.13: June 19, 1968
  - Item 40: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.14: July 24, 1968
  - Item 41: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Item 42: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.15: August 21, 1968
  - Item 43: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.2, June 1967
  - Item 44: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.3, July 1967
  - Item 45: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.5: September 1967
  - Item 46: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.6: October 1967
  - Item 47: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.7: November/December 1967
  - Item 48: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.8: January 17, 1968
  - Item 49: Industrial News, TUC Incomes Policy Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.9: February 1968
  - Item 50: Trade Union News for Overseas, 1967; Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.125, December 1967
- Box: 38, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: TGWU Organisation and Structure, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
    Author: Transport and General Workers Union
  - Item 2: Trades Union Congress East Anglia Region: Rules of the Regional Council as at 20.4.85, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The Story of the TGWU, 1975; Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Box: 38, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: ICC views on a un code of conduct for multinational enterprises -- Document No. 191/95 Rev., 1976; Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Author: International Chamber of Commerce
  - Item 2: The Colombo Plan: A Summary, 1950; Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Notes: extracts from the plan
  - Item 3: Workers' Councils and Worker Participation in Management in Theory and in Actuality, 1971; Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Author: Morris D. Forkosch
    Notes: article from Washburn Law Journal, vol.10, no.3 (1971)
- Box: 38, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Bookers Stores Limited and the Clerical and Commercial Workers Union for the Avoidance and Settlement of Disputes, 1965; Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Author: British Guiana United Broadcasting Company, Limited; Clerical & Commercial Workers' Union
  - Item 2: Memorandum of Agreement between Guiana Merchants Limited and the Clerical and Commercial Workers Union in respect of wages and conditions of employment, 1964; Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Author: Guiana Merchants Limited; Clerical and Commercial Workers' Union
  - Item 3: Memorandum of agreement between British Guiana United Broadcasting Company, Limited and the Clerical & Commercial Workers' Union, 1965; Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Agreement between G. Bettencourt & Company Limited and the Clerical & Commercial Workers' Union, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Author: G. Bettencourt & Company Limited; Clerical & Commercial Workers' Union
  - Item 5: Memorandum of agreement between Guiana Merchants Limited and the Clerical and Commercial Workers' Union, 1964; Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Memorandum of agreement between British Guiana United Broadcasting Company, Limited and the Clerical & Commercial Workers' Union, 1965; Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Memorandum of agreement between B.G. Lithographic Company Limited and the Clerical and Commercial Workers' Union, 1964; Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Author: B.G. Lithographic Company Limited; Clerical & Commercial Workres' Union
  - Item 8: Memorandum of agreement between Wieting & Richter Limited and the Clerical & Commercial Workers' Union, 1965; Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Author: Wieting & Richter Limited; Clerical & Commercial Workers' Union
- Box: 38, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Analysis of Working Conditions and Fringe Benefits 1967-1969, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
    Author: British Columbia Federation of Labour (C.C.L.)
  - Item 2: Canadian Labour Congress, Affiliated Local Unions in British Columbia - Sixth Statistical Summary of Wage Rates, Increases and Major Working Conditions, 1968; Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Memorandum in Support of Proposed Legislation submitted by the British Columbia Federation of Labour to the Honourable W.A.C. Bennet, Premier and Members of the Provincial Cabinet, 1970; Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Submission by the British Columbia Federation of Labour to the Industrial Relations Board concerning Minimum Wages, 1969; Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: The British Columbia Federation of Labour submission to the Human Rights Commission in the matter of the Human Rights Act, 1969; Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: To Recording Secretaries of Affiliated Locals: Revised List of Publications - March 1970, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Box: 38, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Labour News Headlines, 1977; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Author: Labour Canada
    Notes: v.9:no. 214
  - Item 2: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.124
  - Item 3: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.125
  - Item 4: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.126
  - Item 5: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.127
  - Item 6: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.128
  - Item 7: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.129
  - Item 9: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.130
  - Item 10: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.132
  - Item 12: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.134
  - Item 13: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.135
  - Item 14: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.136
  - Item 15: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.137
  - Item 17: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.123
  - Item 18: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.122
  - Item 19: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.121
  - Item 20: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.120
  - Item 21: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.119
  - Item 22: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.118
  - Item 23: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.117
  - Item 24: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.116
  - Item 25: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.115
  - Item 26: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.114
  - Item 27: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.113
  - Item 28: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.112
  - Item 29: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.111
  - Item 30: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.110
  - Item 31: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.109
  - Item 32: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.108
  - Item 33: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.15
  - Item 34: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.16
  - Item 35: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 36: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.18
  - Item 37: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.19
  - Item 38: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.20
  - Item 39: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.22
  - Item 40: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.24
  - Item 41: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.25
  - Item 42: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.26
  - Item 43: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.27
  - Item 44: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.106
  - Item 45: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.107
  - Item 46: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.105
  - Item 47: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.104
  - Item 48: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.103
  - Item 49: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.102
  - Item 50: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.101
  - Item 51: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.100
  - Item 52: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.99
  - Item 53: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.98
  - Item 54: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.97
  - Item 55: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.96
  - Item 56: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.95
  - Item 57: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.94
  - Item 58: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.93
  - Item 59: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.92
  - Item 60: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.91
  - Item 61: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.90
  - Item 62: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.89
  - Item 63: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.88
  - Item 64: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.87
  - Item 65: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.86
  - Item 66: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.85
  - Item 67: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.84
  - Item 68: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.83
  - Item 69: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.82
  - Item 70: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.81
  - Item 71: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.80
  - Item 72: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.79
  - Item 73: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.78
  - Item 74: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.77
  - Item 75: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.76
  - Item 76: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.75
  - Item 77: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.74
  - Item 78: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.73
  - Item 79: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.72
  - Item 80: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.71
  - Item 81: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.70
  - Item 82: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.69
  - Item 83: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.68
  - Item 84: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.67
  - Item 85: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.66
  - Item 86: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.6
  - Item 87: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.64
  - Item 88: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.63
  - Item 89: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.62
  - Item 90: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.61
  - Item 91: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.60
  - Item 92: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.59
  - Item 93: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.58
  - Item 94: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.57
  - Item 95: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.56
  - Item 96: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.55
  - Item 97: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.54
  - Item 98: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.53
  - Item 99: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.52
  - Item 100: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.51
  - Item 101: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.50
  - Item 102: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.49
  - Item 103: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.48
  - Item 104: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.47
  - Item 105: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.36
  - Item 106: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 107: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.38
  - Item 108: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.39
  - Item 109: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 110: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.40
  - Item 111: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.41
  - Item 112: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 113: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.43
  - Item 114: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 115: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.45
  - Item 116: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.46
  - Item 117: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.35
  - Item 118: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.34
  - Item 119: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.32
  - Item 120: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 121: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.31
  - Item 122: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.30
  - Item 123: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.29
  - Item 124: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.28
  - Item 125: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.14
  - Item 126: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.13
  - Item 127: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.12
  - Item 128: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.11
  - Item 129: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.10
  - Item 130: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.9
  - Item 131: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.8
  - Item 132: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.7
  - Item 133: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 134: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.5
  - Item 135: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.3
  - Item 136: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.2
  - Item 137: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 138: Labour News Headlines, 1978; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.1
  - Item 139: Labour News Headlines, 1977; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.9:no.46
  - Item 140: Labour News Headlines, 1977; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.9:no.246
  - Item 141: Labour News Headlines, 1977; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.9:no.247
  - Item 142: Labour News Headlines, 1977; Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.9:no.344